# **Bryn Bennett**



+64 275215835



https://github.com/LaserFlash



https://laserflash.tk



bryn.t.bennett@gmail.com

### About me ———

I am a graduating IT student from Victoria University having completed the requirements for a B.Sc in Computer Science and additional BE(Hons) papers. Some of my other passions include: yachting, canoe polo, skiing, and gaming. As well as spending a large amount of time completing university projects I have undertaken and worked on some of my own personal projects and balanced this with spending time training for national and international regattas as part of the Wellington Youth Sailing Trust Match Racing Squad.

#### Skills ———

Angular

Firebase

HTML

CSS

React

Git

Java

CSharp

# Language & Frameworks



















IATTTX

# Education

2016 - 2019 **BE(Hons) converted to B.Sc in 2019** 

Majoring in Computer Science

2010 - 2015 NCEA: Level 1, 2, and 3 with Excellence Rongotai College

Web Technology and Programming, Calculus, Physics, Chemistry, Geography, English, Economics

# Work Experience

#### 2019 - present Development Squad Coach

Wellington Youth Sailing Trust

- Coaching a group of 6 teenagers
  - · Setting out a season training plan for the squad
  - Adapting trainings for the conditions and what the sailors will find the most beneficial

Victoria University

#### 2018 Software Development of Employment Website

Pihinga

- Designed and developed a job search platform for solo parents
- Managing development of the project from start to finish as part of a group of six
- Requirement gathering through client interaction
- Balancing client wants with what is feasible with the given time constraints.

#### 2018 - present Web App Development For the Following Yacht Clubs

Tup Radford Intercollegiate Yachting Academy, Queen Charlotte Yacht Club, New Plymouth Yacht Club

- Adaptation of a previously developed web app to the requirements of a different set of clients
- Management of client relationships to deliver fit for purpose products

#### 2017 - present Yacht & Power Boat Maintenance Technician

Wellington Youth Sailing Trust

- Maintenance of small keel boats and a rigid inflatable boat
- Identifying what work is most important and allocating time accordingly
- Prioritising work around upcoming events the boats will be used in
- Purchasing spare parts and reporting to monthly trust meetings

#### 2017 - present Web App Development For Youth Sailing Program

Wellington Youth Sailing Trust

- Designed and developed a web and mobile accessible app for tracking boat maintenance issues, and health and safety documentation
- Researching existing tools and frameworks to help the development of a web app
- Understanding Maritime New Zealand's requirements and the Marine Operators Safety System (MOSS)
- Identifying and communicating the benefits that introducing the system would have on the Trust's processes

### 2013 - present Junior and Adult Learn to Sail Coach

Worser Bay Boating Club

- · Coaching students of all ages and skill levels
- Tailoring sessions to the students and how they learn, practical and theory
- Catering for what the student wants from the course: confidence in a boat, ability to race, just having fun

# **Bryn Bennett**

+64 275215835



https://github.com/LaserFlash



https://laserflash.tk



bryn.t.bennett@gmail.com

Skills -

Angular

Firebase

HTML

CSS

React

Git

Java

CSharp

# Language & Frameworks



















# Volunteer Work

2017 Blind Foundation - 'Have a go sailing day'
2017, 2018 Wellington Marathon - Drink Stations
2015, 2016 Wellington Marathon - Marshal

## Awards

2018

| 2017        | Faculty of Engineering Deans List  | Victoria University |
|-------------|------------------------------------|---------------------|
| 2016        | Excellence Scholarship             | Victoria University |
| 2015        | School Prize Digital Technologies  | Rongotai College    |
| 2013 - 2015 | School Honours Awards for Yachting | Rongotai College    |

# Other Qualifications

| 2017 | Yachting New Zealand - Learn to Sail Coach           |
|------|--|
| 2016 | St John - CPR & Basic First Aid                      |
| 2013 | Yachting New Zealand - Assistant Learn to Sail Coach |
|      |  |

**NZTA - Advanced Driving Skills** 

## Sporting Achievements

| 2019 | NZ Youth Match Racing Worlds Trials - 2nd (crew of 4)          |
|------|--|
| 2019 | Centre Port International Youth Match Racing Regatta - 3rd     |
|      | (crew of 4)  |
| 2018 | Centre Port International Youth Match Racing Regatta - 2nd     |
|      | (crew of 4)  |
| 2017 | Harken International Youth Match Racing Regatta (Sydney) - 6th |
|      | (crew of 5)  |
| 2016 | Nespresso Youth Match Racing - 3rd (crew of 5)                 |
| 2016 | Centre Port International Youth Match Racing Regatta - 3rd     |
|      | (crew of 4)  |
| 2016 | Musto International Youth Match Racing Regatta (Sydney) - 5th  |
|      | (crew of 5)  |
| 2016 | Harken International Youth Match Racing Regatta (Sydney) - 6th |
|      | (crew of 5)  |
| 2014 | NZ Youth Match Racing Nationals - 1st and National Champion    |
|      | (crew of 4)  |
| 2014 | Nespresso Youth Match Racing Regatta - 1st (crew of 5)         |
| 2013 | College Sport Wellington Regional Canoe Polo Champion          |
|      | (team of 7)  |
| 2013 | NZ Rep at Laser 4.7 Youth Worlds, Lake Balaton Hungary         |
| 2013 | NZ Laser 4.7 Nationals - 1st and National Champion             |
|      |  |